Ending
Yoo-hoo!
Hello.
I'm Renka Iwamoto.
I'm Satsuki Kawahara
Yay!
Satsuki, where are we?
Yes, we are here in Sapporo, Hokkaido.
Yay!
We are currently on a nationwide tour.
We're performing at the Setsusui Heim Ice Arena in Sapporo.
We just finished our performance in Hokkaido.
We would like to announce our plan right away!
What shall we eat on the national tour?
in Hokkaido
We did it last year in the studio.
But since we're going to be in Hokkaido, we thought it would be a good idea to have some delicious food there.
So we thought it would be nice if we could have some delicious food there.
Satsuki-chan is holding something like a board.
She's holding something like a board.
What is this?
Shall I show it to you?
Let me see.
Ta-da!
Since we came all the way to Hokkaido for the tour...
Why don't you eat the whole thing?
Mr. Hanakawa isn't here today.
Actually, I wanted to come with you because of our schedule.
But I've heard about all kinds of good places.
Isn't that good?
That's right.
I'm going to write about it here.
I want to eat good food, don't you?
Let's eat!
Time to write!writing time
scribble, scribble, scribble, scribble
I made a mistake
Yes, I wrote a little.
Here it is.
It may be a little hard to read...
Since we came all the way to Hokkaido on a tour, why don't we have a seafood bowl at Yahasen Fish Restaurant?
Why don't you have a bowl of seafood at Yonpachi Sen Fish Restaurant?
Yes!
Let's go there right away!
Let's go!
GongGong!
Do you want some seafood? Tuna.
I love tuna.
But all seafood in Hokkaido is delicious.
Crab...
I love crab!
Hokkaido is nice, isn't it?
Hokkaido's nice.
What a nature!
There's a lot of national tours this year.
The Burchell region.
Where are you looking forward to?
I've never been to Okinawa.
I see.
I'm looking forward to it.
I've never been.
But I'm not so good in the heat.
I'm not sure how hot it's going to be.
Is the key to success.
But if I say it's hot...
It's not Jingu.
We can't win against Jingu.
The heat is...
Wow.Wow.
Let's head out.
They're almost here.
Oh, my gosh.
I can't wait.
I'm starving.
What have you eaten today?
I haven't eaten anything.
This is the time I'm filming now.
So-so.
Well, it's getting late in the evening.
Well, it's about the time I finished lunch.
It's about the right time.
I haven't eaten anything.
I'm starving.
I'm sure you'll be able to taste the best
I'm sure you can taste it.
Seafood when you're really hungry.
I'm so happy!
I love it! I love it! I love it!
This is it!
Four Thousand and One Fish Heaven
Oh...
It's so hard.
Four thousand eight hundred and eighty thousand fish.
Yes!
Here it comes.
Please.
Wow!
So many crabs.
Oh, my God.
This is a specialty store!
Excuse me, I'm Renka Iwamoto.Excuse me, I'm Renka Iwamoto.
Yes, hello, please hold.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
We're here.
The menu is right here.
The back.
We have it right here.
Oh, there's so many!
I want some!
What should I do?
I want
Fresh Trotter Salmon Negitoro Bowl
Negitoro Ramen
what should I eat?
I personally would like the Seafood Negitoro Ramen
Such a variety!
I didn't expect there to be so many!
The other ones look delicious too!
Yes, it says so on the back!
Looks delicious!
Isn't it amazing?
It says "Aburi Mentaiko" (roasted cod roe)!
Oh no!
I love it.
Have you had many chances to talk to him lately?
Yes.
How's it going?
What do you think?
I can't look at Mr. Renka's face for more than 10 seconds.
Ten seconds is the limit.
Look her in the eye.
I can't look at her face.
No, that's not what I meant.No, that's not what I meant.
If I look into your eyes for more than 10 seconds, I'm gonna...
What, what, what, what?
I get a smirk on my face.
I've been thinking about it a lot lately.
I think it's a little creepy.
But it's cute!
Cute.
Well, I can't go into details, but...
Yes, it is.
During rehearsal, you and Lenka face each other.
We have a rather long period of time.
Lenka's watching you the whole time.
Yes, I knew that Lenka was watching us from the rehearsal.
I knew that she was watching me.
But it didn't work.
No matter how many times I tried, it didn't work.
She's really cute from the beginning.
That's what my juniors tell me.
That's all that matters.
I don't care if it's a lie or not.
It's not a lie, it's not a lie, it's not a lie.
Yes, it is.
I finished slowly.
Yes, ma'am.
Salmon menu.
Ta-da!
Wow!
Self-insert
Dooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Ta-da!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Do... do...
That's awesome, that's brilliant.
Soy Sauce InsertSoy Sauce Insert
Soy Sauce
This one is thick.
This one is light.
The other one is all-purpose.
All-purpose
This one is here.
And here is Sachiki!
She's so cute!
How is it?
It looks delicious.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Looks delicious!
Looks delicious.
Oh, my God.
It smells so good.
It's so good.
Lalalala!
They both shine!
They're both shining!
Lenka and the seafood bowl are both shining!
This negitoro looks like it's about to fall off.
Indeed, it's incredible...
Yes.
It's showing a little.
Yes, it is.
Wow, how do you cook it?
I'm using this to keep my hands warm.
-Oh? Let's eat! -Let's eat.
I've never really eaten salmon.
-What? Yes, I have.
You just said tuna.
I only eat tuna.
Let's see Lenka in profile.
Oh no... I'll have the salmon.
What?What?
Almost the first salmon in my life.
What? Really?
Wow, it's so pretty from every angle.
Sweet!
Is it good?
Yes, it is! It's so good!
He's got a big sparkle in his eye.
It's so good.
Wow, it was really good!
Let's try it again, Sasatsuke!
It's so good!
I'll eat it, I'll eat it, I'll eat it!
I hope it won't fall apart and drip.
I can't guarantee that.
I just cracked it open.
But it's okay.
You're doing a great job.
You're doing a great job, aren't you?
It was a lie.
It's a lie.
Well, it can't be helped.
Seafood only.
Dip them in egg and hot water.
Bon appétit!
How is it?
It's so yukke!
It tastes like yukke!
It's delicious.
It's so good!
And the meat is so thick.
It's very chewy.
That's a good report.
He's so cute.
It's delicious.Delicious.
It's so good!
Let's eat.
What should we do with the negitoro?
Will it fall?
It's going to fall.
So we do it like this or like this.
Once.
That's right.
Wait a minute.
Quite a bit.
That's a lot of food.
That's a lot of negitoro.
I love negitoro. I want some negitoro.
I'll put some thick sauce on it. It's amazing.
It's the real thing. It's amazing.
Oh, man!
Oh!
It's really thick.
But it's mild.
Oh, wow.
It's so good!
So mild!
Seafood is good.
Yes, it is.
I'll have to try the shrimp when I get here.
Definitely.
Wow, that's really great.
Ask a local.
Yeah.
It's so important.
The local people.
What should I do? I can't get any food at all.
I feel like I'm the one who's dismantling the place.
It's difficult, isn't it?It's hard, isn't it?
It's hard.
Yes, it's Renca's first time having dinner.
It's so good!
Your chopsticks are going twice as fast as usual.
Yes, of course.
So cute!
I'm so happy!
I'm happy, aren't I?
It's really nice.
Eating a delicious meal.
Talking with Renca like this.
I still haven't had dinner with my juniors.
You too?
No, I haven't.
But... when YoonA came to my house...
Hmmm...
To see the cat.
Oh, yeah, a kitty.
Yes, a cat.
I have a cat named Rute.
I live alone and I have him.
Yes?
Actually...
I have a second cat.
Wow!
The one that's going to die.
Actually, I have a second dog.
Crackle, crackle, crackle!
Excuse me. Excuse me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I didn't tell you.
His name is Sonu.
Oh!
I'm Rute and this is Sonu.This is Mr. Rute and Mr. Sonu.
Cute!
The best
The best!
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious!
It was so good!
It was so delicious!
I was so happy!
So I would like to go to one more restaurant...
Where shall we go next?
Well, may I write again?
Please excuse my writing time.
Yes, please.
It's pretty cold.
It's cold.
When it's cold, it's cold.
It's open.
Yes, sir.
Ta-da!
It's a sweet potato rice cake from Kaiten Sushi Nagoya Family!
Imo mochi (sweet potato cake)!
Look at that!
I thought it would be seafood again, since it's called "Kaiten Sushi", but...
But it's a sweet potato cake!
Ima-fu
Wow!
A lot of people come from here.
It's a sweet potato cake!
How about a taro cake?
I don't know.
I don't know much.
Not much.too much
I can't...
I can't stand up.
I'm a brick against the wind.
I'd like a drink.
Windy.
All back.
Let's go.
Here we go.
This way, please.
Where is it?
This way, sir.
We've arrived at Nagoya Family.
Yay!
Ta-da!
This way!
This way, this way!
Wow!
It's so gorgeous!
This is a Nagoya family.
Wow!
It's written, wow!
Come in, come in!
Excuse me, what do you recommend?
I recommend the salmon roe.
Oh, salmon roe!
Before the rush rush.
Oh, wow!
That's great!
By the way, I heard that taro mochi is also delicious.
The imo mochi is delicious too!
Is it popular?
Yes, it is.
I'll order the imo mochi.
For now...for now
In the meantime, two things.
I'll take two, please.
Wow, there are so many menus!
There are so many menus!
It's amazing.
If you can't read novels, you don't want to see this.
I think I kind of get it.
Isn't this it? Spillage.
Oh, this. A demonstration.
Demonstration?
I bet it's in Hokkaido.
Wow!
- Thank you!
- It's got something on it.
- Butter? Butter? Inserts?
I'm not sure I'll be able to get a good shot.
- Tomorrow's the pictures, right? Tomorrow's the pictures.
Here we go.
- Here you go.
Here you go.
De, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de, de...
He's so cute.
I think I have a good sense of how to take pictures of people.
- You do?
I do have a flair for taking cute pictures of people.
- Really? Then, please.
It's so hot.
- Hot?
- Yes, sir.
- Do we eat it with this?
- Sure, I'll press the front.
- It's kind of hard around the edges.
- What?
- Then I'll eat it.
- Here you go, go ahead.- Yes, please, please, please.
We're ready for you, too.
Bon appétit.
Is it good?
Sweet.
Oh, it's sweet.
It's like a candy.
It's so cute!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It was so cute!
I'm sorry.
I can't look at it.
It's delicious.
Oh, my God.
I want this video.
I want this footage.
It's so good.
It's really hard.
Yeah, it's really crispy.
I'm going to eat it as it is.
Bon appétit.
Hmm?
The santabata dumplings.
Ah!
The three blades of dumplings.
Sauce?
I know, I know.
There's sauce in it too.
It's like that, right?
It's not as firm as I thought it would be.
Yeah, it's...
Easy to chew.
It's chewy. -Really?
It's so good! You can eat this at a sushi restaurant!
It's amazing. Isn't it amazing?That's not good. It's not amazing.
It's amazing.
Hmmm...
I don't want to eat that salmon roe you recommended.
I don't want to eat it.
Since we came all the way to Hokkaido.
I want to eat it, right?
I'll order this one.
But the truth is, I can only order what you recommended.
I can't order it.
It was recommended to me because of the potato.
Yes, potato rice cakes!
Listen a little.
Let's just listen.
Excuse me
Spilled roasted salmon roe...
I recommend it.
I highly recommend it.
Shall I order some?
I'll order it.
It was recommended to me.
I knew I should order what you recommended.
Since we're having seafood sushi...
If I don't have sushi, I won't feel like I'm here.
I don't feel like I've come here unless I have sushi.
Oh, wow!
Please let one person in.
Thank you very much.
Yes, we got your order from around here.
Yes, we'll bring lots of energy, lots of hands.
Let's do it!
Let's go!
Let's do it!heave-ho!
Yes, you can order from around here.
Thank you very much.
Here you go.
You are recommended. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Wow, it's spilling. It's spilling.
The level of spilled salmon roe is amazing. It's a very flashy presentation.
It's amazing.
But it's so much fun.
I'm so surprised.
Now I'm surprised.
Will you take it?
I'll take it.
It's not bad, is it?
I'll take it, I'll take it, I'll take it.
Is it bad?
Oh, my God! Oh, man!
Puchi puchi!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Very rich salmon roe!
Wow, that's not a normal amount of salmon roe!
Yes, it is!
I'll have some then.
I'll try my best to take a bite!
It looks like it's going to spill!
Bon appétit!
Oh, good, good, good.
Mmmm!
Mmm-hmm.
Is it good?
Yeah, it's good.
Oh, my God!That's great!
That's great!
It's like...
It's like the first time I ate salmon roe.
I know.
Wow, Hokkaido is amazing!
Ha-ha-ha!
Hokkaido is amazing!
Oh, that's nice.
Mmm.
Mmm...
nenrin
Thank you for the seino!
It was delicious
I felt like I was in Hokkaido
I was so happy.
It was delicious!
Yes, that's right, Kaiten Sushi!
Nagoya's home made sweet potato rice cake and salmon roe!
It was so delicious!
It was delicious!
I'm so happy!
I've never had salmon roe before.
The salmon roe was delicious!
It was delicious.
So it's different in each region.
There seems to be one for each region.
It looks like each member is going to do it.
I'm sure you'll enjoy it too.
Osaka is next, isn't it?
That's right. Osaka is next.
What will we eat?
Which member will go there?
Please look forward to it.
Thank you very much.Thank you.
Please subscribe to our channel!
It was Satsuki
It was Renca
It was Renka!
Bye-bye!
Bye-bye, it was delicious!